<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_menu">"About "</string>
    <string name="description_subtitle">DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_hint_milestone">Alarm Name</string>
    <string name="delete_menu">Delete</string>
    <string name="sagittarius">Sagittarius</string>
    <string name="capricorn">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="aquarius">Aquarius</string>
    <string name="pisces">Pisces</string>
    <string name="taurus">Taurus</string>
    <string name="gemini">Gemini</string>

    <!-- phrases -->
    <string name="phrase_enero_1">"“I am convinced that at least half of what separates successful entrepreneurs from unsuccessful ones is sheer perseverance” - Steve Jobs"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_2">"“Wealth, after all, is a relative thing, since he who has little and wants less is richer than he who has more and wants even more.” - Charles Caleb Colton"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_3">"“You can't save people, you can just love them”: Anaïs Nin"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_4">"“The way to hit the nail once is to hit the horseshoe a hundred times”: Colonel Sanders"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_5">"“He who loses money, loses a lot; the one who loses a friend; lose even more; he who loses faith loses everything”: Eleanor Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_6">"“Keep a global vision while attending to the daily details”: Donald Trump</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_7">"“Do what you can, with what you have, where you are”: Theodore Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_8">"“No matter how many times you fail, you only have to be right once. Then everyone will call you an overnight success and tell you how lucky you are” – Mark Cuban"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_9">"“Never go the way you have set out, because it leads where others have already been” - Alexander Graham Bell"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_10">"“If you don't like to take risks, you should run out of business”: Ray Kroc"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_11">"“Success is 1%% inspiration and 99%% perspiration” - Thomas Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_12">"“Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work and the only way to do it is to love what you do.”: Anonymous"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_13">"“Always keep your eyes open, Always watching. Because anything you see can inspire you”: Grace Coddington"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_14">"“If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. As with everything that has to do with the heart, you will know when you have found it” - Steve Jobs"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_15">"“Opportunities don't happen, they are created”: Chris Grosser"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_16">"“Only buy something you are happy with if the market closes in 10 years” – Warren Buffett</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_17">"“You cannot escape the responsibility of tomorrow by avoiding it today” - Abraham Lincoln</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_18">"“Money doesn't make you happy, but it calms your nerves”: Sean O'Casey"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_19">"“I really am a practical dreamer; my dreams are not trifles in the air. What I want is to make my dreams come true”: Mahatma Gandi</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_20">"“There are many bad reasons to start a business. But there's only one good reason, and I think you know what it is: to change the world.” Phil Libin"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_21">"“Always give more than what is expected of you”: Larry Page</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_22">"“Move fast and break objects. If you're not breaking things, you're not moving fast enough.” - Mark Zuckerberg"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_23">"“The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams”: Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_24">"“Take your first step with faith, you don't have to see the whole ladder, just take your first step” - Martin Luther King"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_25">"“Money is often very expensive”: Ralph Waldo Emerson"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_26">"“An optimist sees an opportunity in every calamity, a pessimist sees a calamity in every opportunity” – Winston Churchill"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_27">"“Our greatest glory does not consist in never having fallen, but in having risen after each fall”: Confucius"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_28">"“The most important thing to do if you're in a hole is to stop digging” - Warren Buffett"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_29">"“I hate how people think 'glass half empty' when in reality their glass is almost full. I am grateful when I have one more drop in the glass because I know exactly what to do with it” – Gary Vaynerchuk"</string>
    <string name="phrase_enero_30">"“It is hard to fail, but it is even worse never to have tried to succeed.” - Theodore Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_1">"“People can be very smart or have skills that are applicable, but if they don't believe in it, then they're not going to work really hard” - Mark Zuckerberg"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_2">"“Our greatest weakness is to give up, the only way to succeed is to always try one more time” - Thomas Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_3">"“I've found that the harder I work, the luckier I get” - Thomas Jefferson"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_4">"“Buy when everyone else is selling and save money when everyone else is buying. It is not a slogan. It is the essence of successful investments”: J. Paul Getty</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_5">"“There is no substitute for hard work” – Thomas Edison</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_6">"“Most people miss out on opportunities because they dress normal and look like work” – Thomas Edison</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_7">"“I think it's easier to move forward on mega-ambitious dreams”: Larry Page"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_8">"“There is a rule for the businessman and it is: make products with the highest possible quality at the lowest cost and paying the highest possible wages”: Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_9">"“Sharing ideas without processing them can lead us into the delusion of thinking that we are actually doing something, when in fact we are not doing anything”: Charles T. Lee"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_10">"“The habit of saving is an education; encourages every virtue, teaches self-control, cultivates a sense of order, trains foresight, and broadens the mind”: TT Munger"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_11">"“Don't waste your time banging on a wall, hoping to transform it into a door”: Coco Chanel"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_12">"“How you deal with failure determines how you achieve success” – David Feherty</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_13">"“Experience taught me that the best investments are the ones you don't make”: Donald Trump"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_14">"“Watch, listen and learn. You can't know everything. Anyone who thinks they know everything is destined for mediocrity”: Donald Trump"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_15">"“Try the impossible to improve your work”: Brian Tracy"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_16">"“If you can dream it you can do it, remember that all this began with a mouse”: Walt Disney"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_17">"“There are only two ways to live your life. One is to think that nothing is a miracle. The other is to think that everything is a miracle ”: Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_18">"“If it scares you, it might be a good thing to try”: Seth Godin"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_19">"“I definitely wanted to earn my freedom. But the main motivation was not to make money, but to make an impact”: Sean Parker"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_20">"“Lack of money is the root of all evil” - Mark Twain"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_21">"“You can only live once. And I don't want to waste a minute of my life.” - Richard Branson"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_22">"“Man discovers himself when he measures himself against an obstacle”: Antoine de Saint Exupery</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_23">"“Failure is only the opportunity to start over more intelligently” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_24">"“A business absolutely dedicated to service will have only one concern about profits: they will be too great” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_25">"“Some people don't like change, but you need to embrace it if the alternative is disaster”: Elon Musk"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_26">"“Do what you love and the money will follow”: Marsha Sinetar</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_27">"“To succeed, we must first believe that we can”: Nikos Kazantzakis"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_28">"“Success is a lousy teacher. Seduce smart people into thinking they can't lose.” - Bill Gates"</string>
    <string name="phrase_febrero_29">"“If you fall seven times, get up eight”: Nana Koribi Yaoki"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_1">"“When you have money, only you remember who you are. But when you don't have money, everyone forgets who you are. Such is life” – Bill Gates"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_2">"“The best way to predict the future is to invent it” - Alan Key"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_3">"“Whether you think you can, or you think you can't, you're right” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_4">"“Success is connected to action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes but they never give up” – Conrad Hilton</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_5">"“If we had to talk more than listen, we would have two mouths and only one ear” - Mark Twain"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_6">"“The biggest risk is not taking any. In a world that is changing so fast, the only strategy that is guaranteed to fail is not taking risks.” – Mark Zuckerberg"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_7">"“To do or not to do. There is no use trying, only doing”: Yoda"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_8">"“Money can't buy friends, but you can buy a new kind of enemy”: Spike Milligan"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_9">"“You will be successful because most people are lazy”: Shahir Zag"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_10">"“Do something that scares you every day”: Anonymous"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_11">"“Don't try to be original, just try to be good”: Paul Rand"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_12">"“You are a successful person when you have some of the things money can buy and all the things money can't buy” - Zig Ziglar"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_13">"“There are only two days in the year when nothing can be done. One is called yesterday and the other one tomorrow. Therefore, today is the ideal day to love, grow, do, and mainly live”: Dalai Laima"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_14">"“Fear exists nowhere else except in the mind” – Dale Carnegie</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_15">"“A coward is incapable of showing love; doing so is reserved for the brave” – Mahatma Gandi</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_16">"“There are men that fight one day and are good. There are others that fight for a year and are better. Some fight for many years and are very good. But there are those who struggle all their lives. Those are the essentials”: Bertolt Brecht"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_17">"“Money can't buy life”: Bob Marley"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_18">"“Money is a tool. It will take you where you want, but it will not replace you as a driver”: Ayn Rand"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_19">"“Time, perseverance, and ten years of trying will eventually make you look like an overnight success.” - Biz Stone"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_20">"“Optimism is the quality most associated with success and happiness” – Brian Tracy</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_21">"“It took me 20 years to be successful overnight”: Woody Allen"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_22">"“Risking more than others think is safe. Dreaming more than others think is practical” – Howard Schultz</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_23">"“Making money in itself is not difficult. The difficult thing is to earn it by doing something worth dedicating your life to”: Carlos Ruiz Zafón</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_24">"“Don't worry about financing if you don't need it. Today it is cheaper than ever to start a business”: Noah Everett</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_25">"“In the ideas is where our strength lies and all the better if we hold them with obstinacy”: Enzo Ferrari</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_26">"“Keep in mind that your purpose and your plan to achieve it can be modified from time to time… the important thing is that you understand the meaning of always working with an objective in mind and with a well-structured plan”: Napoleon Hill</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_27">"“If you double the number of experiments you do per year, you will double your ingenuity”: Jeff Bezos"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_28">"“Stop chasing money and start chasing passion”: Tony Hsieh"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_29">"“Wealth does not consist in having great possessions, but in having few needs”: Epithet"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_30">"“Sometimes you win, sometimes you learn” - John Maxwell"</string>
    <string name="phrase_marzo_31">"“You are only as good as the people you hire”: Ray Kroc</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_1">"“If you double the number of experiments you do per year, you will double your ingenuity”: Jeff Bezos"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_2">"“Stop chasing money and start chasing passion”: Tony Hsieh"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_3">"“Wealth does not consist in having great possessions, but in having few needs”: Epithet"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_4">"“Sometimes you win, sometimes you learn” - John Maxwell"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_5">"“You are only as good as the people you hire”: Ray Kroc</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_6">"“Intelligence is a gift, kindness is a choice”: Jeff Bezos"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_7">"“Simplicity and common sense should be the basis of strategic planning and direction”: Ingvar Kamprad</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_8">"“Success is learning to go from failure to failure without despairing” - Winston Churchill"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_9">"“Price is what you pay, value is what you get” - Warren Buffett"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_10">"“Never spend your money before you have it”: Thomas Jefferson"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_11">"“I owe my success to listening respectfully to the best advice, and then disappearing and doing the exact opposite”: GK Chesterton"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_12">"“A business that makes nothing but money is a poor business” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_13">"“When you innovate, you have to be prepared for people to tell you that you are crazy”: Larry Ellison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_14">"“Those who say something cannot be done are often interrupted by others who are doing it”: Joel A. Barker</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_15">"“Those who quit are more numerous than those who fail” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_16">"“While money cannot buy happiness, it allows you to choose your own form of misery” - Groucho Marx"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_17">"“Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through the trial-and-error experience of suffering can the soul be strengthened, ambition be inspired, and success ultimately achieved”: Helen Keller"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_18">"“Life is dangerous, not because of those who do evil, but because of those who sit and watch what happens” - Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_19">"“People are not remembered by the number of times they fail, but by the number of times they succeed” - Thomas Alva Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_20">"“Each person forges their own destiny”: Carlos Slim</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_21">"“You can say anything to people, but the way you say it determines how they react” – John Rampton"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_22">"“I think it's possible for normal people to choose to be extraordinary”: Elon Musk"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_23">"“Success is how high you bounce after you hit rock bottom” – George Patton</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_24">"“Competition makes you better, always, always makes you better, even if the competitor wins”: Carlos Slim"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_25">"“Numbing the pain for a while will make you feel it more intensely later.” - Albus Dumbledore"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_26">"“All progress takes place outside the comfort zone” – Michael John Bobak</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_27">"“It is better to do the most insignificant thing in the world, than spend half an hour doing nothing” - Goethe"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_28">"“Never lower your head, always look up, win or lose”: Enzo Ferrari"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_29">"“He who thinks he knows everything is closing doors”: Donald Trump"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_30">"“I have not failed. I have found 10,000 ways that don't work.” - Thomas Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_abril_31">"“Outstanding leaders go out of their way to build self-esteem in their staff. If people believe in themselves, it's amazing what they can achieve.” - Sam Walton"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_1">"“If you can't fly, run, if you can't run, walk, if you can't walk, crawl. No matter what you do, keep moving forward” – Martin Luther King Jr."</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_2">"“Rule number 1: never lose money. Rule number 2: never forget rule number 1” – Warren Buffett</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_3">"“It is not the man who has little, but the one who wants more who is poor”: Seneca"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_4">"“What really shapes our lives is the meaning we give to things” - Tony Robbins"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_5">"“Persistence is very important. You should not resign unless you are forced to resign” – Elon Musk</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_6">"“Friends and good manners will take you where money can't” - Margaret Walker"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_7">"“If you only work on things that you like and are passionate about, you shouldn't have a master plan to see how everything turns out”: Mark Zuckerberg"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_8">"“Don't think that money does everything or you will end up doing everything for money”: Voltaire"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_9">"“When a dream appears, grab it!”: Larry Page"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_10">"“Failure is a great opportunity to start again more intelligently” - Henry Ford"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_11">"“To invent, you need a good imagination and a pile of garbage” – Thomas Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_12">"“Money and success don't change people; they simply amplify what is already there” – Will Smith</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_13">"“There is only one class in the community that thinks more about money than the rich, and that is the poor”: Oscar Wilde"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_14">"“Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn't do than the ones you did do. So cast off your moorings, sail away from safe harbors, catch the favorable winds in your sails. Explore. Dream”: Mark Twain"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_15">"“Nothing is particularly difficult if you break it down into small jobs”: Henry Ford Quotes"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_16">"“A little effort is the best substitute for excuses”: Donald Trump"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_17">"“You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore”: Christopher Columbus</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_18">"“Formal education will give you a living; self-education will make you a fortune” – Jim Rohn</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_19">"“It takes 20 years to create a reputation and five minutes to ruin it. If you think that way, you will do things differently.” – Warren Buffet"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_20">"“Money is a terrible master but an excellent servant”: PT Barnum"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_21">"“Somebody sits today in the shade of a tree they planted long ago” – Warren Buffett</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_22">"“Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The surest way to succeed is always to try one more time.” - Thomas Edison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_23">"“Money may not buy happiness, but I'd rather cry in a jaguar than on a bus”: Françoise Sagan"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_24">"“Celebrate your success. Find some humor in your failures” – Sam Walton</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_25">"“A person should set his goals as soon as possible and devote all his energy and talent to them”: Walt Disney</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_26">"“Don't let the fear of losing outweigh the thrill of winning”: Robert Kiyosaki"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_27">"“Money can't buy happiness, but it sure will buy you a better kind of memory” – Ronald Reagan"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_28">"“Money doesn't buy happiness, but it relieves stress”: Besa Kosova"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_29">"“Choose a job you like, and you will never have to work a single day in your life.” - Confucius"</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_30">"“I never try to make money in the stock market. I buy on the assumption that they could close the next day and reopen in 10 years.” – Warren Buffett</string>
    <string name="phrase_mayo_31">"“Only those who are asleep do not make mistakes”: Ingvar Kamprad"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_1">"“Not everything that can be counted counts and not everything that counts can be counted” - Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_2">"“The obstinate will to pursue one's own ambition is truly a force that can overcome obstacles”: Enzo Ferrari</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_3">"“I have never dreamed of success. I have always worked to achieve it”: Estée Lauder</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_4">"“Time is your most important resource. You can do so much in ten minutes. Ten minutes, once past, are gone forever. Ten minutes is not just one sixth of an hour. Divide your life into units of ten minutes and waste as few as possible on meaningless activities”: Ingvar Kamprad"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_5">"“If you really want to do something, you find a way. If not, you will find an excuse”: Jim Rohn"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_6">"“You don't need to have a company of 100 people to develop that idea”: Larry Page</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_7">"“Whenever they ask you if you can do a job, answer yes and immediately start learning how to do it”: Franklin D. Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_8">"“We decided to go ahead, despite the risks and going against reason, because we believe that the path that others have chosen is the right one and the best thing to do”: Howard Schultz"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_9">"“My biggest motivation? Keep challenging myself. I see life as a long university education that I never had – every day I am learning something new”: Richard Branson</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_10">"“We fall to succeed”: Mary Kay Ash</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_11">"“No man should receive a dollar unless that dollar is justly earned.” - Theodore Roosevelt"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_12">"“The Internet should be a means of communication between peoples that contributes to world peace and that the main objective of high technology is to improve people's standard of living”: Larry Ellison"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_13">"“Do not try to become a man of success but a man of values”: Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_14">"“The first step is to establish that something is possible; then the probability will happen”: Elon Musk</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_15">"“You can be young without money, but you can't be old without it”: Tennessee Williams"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_16">"“Too many people spend the money they earned to buy things they don't want, to impress people they don't like” - Will Rogers"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_17">"“There is a difference between being poor and being broke. One can be temporarily broke, one is poor for life”: Robert Kiyosaki"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_18">"“When you are 80 years old, and in a quiet moment of reflection, narrating only for yourself the most personal version of your life story, the story that will be most concise and meaningful will be the series of choices you have made. In the end, we are our choices” – Jeff Bezos"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_19">"“Never give up on a dream for as long as it may take. In the same way, time will pass ”: Earl Nightingale"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_20">"“In investing, what is comfortable is rarely profitable” – Robert Arnott"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_21">"“When you stop dreaming you stop living” - Malcolm Forbes"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_22">"“You can be disappointed if you fail, but you're done if you don't try” - Beverly Sills"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_23">"“Failure is not losing, it is not having tried”: Xavier Gabriel"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_24">"“A champion is afraid of losing. Others are afraid of winning”: Billie Jean King</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_25">"“A person who never made a mistake, never tried something new”: Albert Einstein"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_26">"“The way bosses treat employees is exactly how employees will treat customers” – Sam Walton</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_27">"“It's okay to have money and the things that money can buy, but it's also okay to check from time to time that you haven't lost the things that money can't buy” - George Lorimer"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_28">"“If you are not embarrassed by the first version of your product, you launched it too late”: Reid Hoffman"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_29">"“The comfort zone is a wonderful place, but nothing grows there”: Anonymous"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_30">"“You will become as small as the desire that controls you, and as large as your dominant aspiration.” - James Allen"</string>
    <string name="phrase_junio_31">"“Mickey Mouse appeared out of my mind in a sketchbook, on a train from Manhattan to Hollywood, at a time when my brother Roy and I's company was at an all time low and disaster seemed just around the corner. corner”: Walt Disney"</string>
    <string name="phrase_julio_1">"“I'm not afraid of dying, I'm afraid of not trying”: Jay Z"</string>
    <string name="hour_speach">It\'s %d:%d</string>
    <string name="temp_speach">The temperature is %,.1f degrees Celsius. Equivalent to %,.1f degrees Fahrenheit</string>
    <string name="thursday">T</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services_string">I have read and accept the</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="snooze">Postpone</string>
    <string name="snack_bar_undo">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="snack_bar_text">Undo delete</string>
    <string name="show_weather_option">Show daily weather</string>
    <string name="selected_vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="selected_postpone">Postpone</string>
    <string name="selected_repeat">Repeat</string>
    <string name="selected_melody">Selected melody</string>
    <string name="select_all_menu">All</string>
    <string name="save_button">SAVE</string>
    <string name="policy_string">I have read and accept the</string>
    <string name="preview_card_menu">Preview</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="wednesday">W</string>
    <string name="rain_chance">Chance of rain %s %%</string>
    <string name="go_Settings">Go Settings</string>
    <string name="monday">M</string>
    <string name="tuesday">T</string>
    <string name="friday">F</string>
    <string name="saturday">S</string>
    <string name="sunday">S</string>
    <string name="discard">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="next_alarm_string">Next alarm</string>
    <string name="no_alarm">No active alarms</string>
    <string name="on_string">On</string>
    <string name="off_string">Off</string>
    <string name="melody">Melody</string>
    <string name="minutes_string">%d minutes</string>
    <string name="hours_string">%d hours</string>
    <string name="hours_string_single">%d hour</string>
    <string name="no_repeat_string">No repeat</string>
    <string name="no_postpone_string">No postpone</string>
    <string name="no_vibrate_string">No vibration</string>
    <string name="no_melody_string">No melody</string>
    <string name="no_alarm_entity">An unexpected error occurred while playing the alarm. Please contact support.</string>
    <string name="delete_alarms_title">Delete alarms?</string>
    <string name="delete_alarms_msg">Are you sure you want to delete the selected alarms?</string>
    <string name="delete_alarm_title">Delete alarm?</string>
    <string name="ring_permission_title">Run in sleep mode</string>
    <string name="ring_permission_msg">You need to grant permissions to the app to allow it to work when the device screen is locked.</string>
    <string name="delete_alarm_msg">Are you sure you want to delete the alarm?</string>
    <string name="alarms_every">Every %s at %s</string>
    <string name="alarms_everyDay">Everyday at %s</string>
    <string name="alarm_today">Today %s %d de %s - %s</string>
    <string name="alarm_tomorrow">Tomorrow %s %d de %s - %s</string>
    <string name="duplicate_card_menu">Duplicate</string>
    <string name="delete_card_menu">Delete</string>
    <string name="brew_personal_desc">I am excited about mobile technologies. Creator of ideas, curious and nature lover.</string>
    <string name="choose_a_file">Choose a melody</string>
    <string name="no_sound">Melody not found</string>

    <string name="scheduled_alarm_msg">Alarm scheduled in %s</string>
    <string name="years">%d years</string>
    <string name="months">%d months</string>
    <string name="days">%d days</string>
    <string name="hours">%d hours</string>
    <string name="minutes">%d minutes</string>
    <string name="show_phrases_option">Show daily phrases</string>
    <string name="no_phrases_string">Hide</string>
    <string name="phrases_string">Show</string>
    <string name="enable_location_snackbar">You need to enable location</string>
    <string name="access_location_permission_snackbar">Allow AlarMe to access the location</string>
    <string name="alarm_sound">Alarm Sound</string>
    <string name="vibration_text">Vibration</string>
    <string name="postpone_text">Postpone</string>
    <string name="repeat_text">Repeat</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services_body">Put your terms of service here</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_body">Put your privacy policy here</string>
    <string name="horoscopeEnable">Horoscope enable</string>
    <string name="show_horoscope_option">Show daily horoscope</string>
</resources>